[{"answer": "Is it", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "She's doing like those Iranians.", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " This could be it", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Let's work on it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Home", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No one's waiting", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You've come to me. I wanted to believe you would one day", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "But you're here. So you must have come to me. ", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "About an hour and a half ago. I saw her come out of a place. She said she was visiting a friend. But she wouldn't tell me who", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "She was very evasive", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "This could be it", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Does what feel comfortable", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Does what feel comfortable", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "This could be it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "The whole thing is my fault. I took unfair advantage of your patience and understanding. You understand me", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And you've been extremely patient", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That's always been my problem", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You know why, don't you? Because I am patient, chai", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "There may be things you'd rather not know about", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I had an affair", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I had an affair", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend, no. This is insupportable. How could you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " I think you're a little confused. Nothing personal friend", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What are we talking about", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes. What are you implying", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why do you care", "docId": "Game-6.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No. They're not your team. They're my team", "qsentId": 30}]